<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="how_to_play_title">How to play</string>

    <string name="tips_and_tricks_title">Tips and Tricks</string>

    <string name="settings_tutorial_title">Settings tutorial</string>
    <string name="settings_tutorial_text">
        Each map comes with recommended settings, but these can be tweaked by the host. Here, we
        describe what each setting affects, so you know exactly what you\’re changing.\n\n
        Here\'s a quick rundown of the settings yo might want to change game to game:\n\n
        - Impostors: This refers to the amount of Impostors in play. The limit refers to the lowest
        number of Impostors allowed (if your lobby isn\’t full, the game can decide to have less
        Impostors).\n
        - Confirm Ejects: With this on, it will tell you if the person you just ejected was an
        Impostor or not. With it off, it won\'t.\n
        - Emergency Meetings: This is the amount of emergency meetings a player can call from the
        center of the map.\n
        - Emergency Cooldown: This is the amount of time you need to wait in between emergency
        meetings. When playing online, having a long cool down stops it being abused.\n
        - Discussion Time: How long in seconds you can discuss Impostors in meetings before you
        vote.\n- Voting Time: How long in seconds you have to vote. Discussions can continue
        during this time. Shorter time limits make the game more intense, longer limits make them
        more methodical.\n- Player Speed: How fast the players move around the ship.\n- Crewmate
        Vision: How far the crewmates can see around the ship.\n- Impostor Vision: How far the
        Impostor can see around the ship. Impostors typically get better vision to make their job
        easier.\n- Kill Cooldown: How long the Impostor must wait in between kills. The more
        Impostors, the longer it should be.\n- Kill Distance: How close (short, normal, or long)
        the Impostor must be to kill someone.\n- Visual Tasks: A few tasks, such as scanning in
        the MedBay, are visual, as in other players can see you. If you are seen doing a visual
        task, that’s proof that you\’re not the Impostor.\n- Common Tasks: These are the most basic
        tasks in the game, and take an average time to complete.\n- Long Tasks: These tasks take
        the longest as the name implies and involve visiting multiple rooms to complete them.\n-
        Short Tasks: These tasks are very short and can be completed quickly, in a single location.
        \n\nTip: Long tasks are better for the Impostor, as it takes longer to win and crewmates
        must travel to different locations, making grouping up more difficult. Shorter tasks are
        better for the crew, as players can be more direct and can finish the list much quicker.
    </string>

    <string name="best_settings_title">Best setting for server</string>
    <string name="best_settings_text">
        Set Up Advice\n\n
        There are various ways you can tweak Among Us depending on what type of game you\'re
        looking for, so we\'ve suggested some game builds below.\n\n
        Frantic games: If you want to play a fast and frenetic game, you should have a quick kill
        cooldown, lots of short tasks, short discussion time and short voting time, plus confirm
        ejects off. This build means the game moves very quickly, with less time for debate and
        long discussions. It also means you\'ll never be fully aware if you ejected an Impostor or
        not until the end of the game. It favors Impostors, though the high amount of short tasks
        do mean the crew doesn\'t have to work as hard to win.\n\n
        Methodical games: This style of game is largely the opposite, and if the fun of Among Us
        comes from the deduction, you\'ll favor this. It features either a long kill cooldown or 2
        emergency meetings (both together is quite unfair on the Impostors), as well as long
        discussion time and long voting time. Together, these two categories can clear 2 and half
        minutes if you really want to get into it, though many players find anything over 90
        seconds to be too long. Confirm ejects are a must for these games, as it lets players
        know if their suspicions were correct. This build favors crewmates, so having more long
        tasks can address the balance, while including visual tasks goes well with the spirit of
        deduction.\n\n
        Player speed offers no real advantage either way, but most players seem to favor something
        between x1 and x1.75, so it\'s best to stick with that when starting out.\n\n
        How many Impostors should I have?\n\n
        It depends on whether you want to lean into the mystery aspect of the game (in which case,
        just have one Impostor), or want to a more pressured playthrough (in which case, have more
        Impostors).\nAs for group sizes, it\'s best to stick to just one Impostor if you have five
        players or less, and to avoid having three Impostors until you have eight or more players.
        Of course, a lot of players stick with a solo Impostor even in a ten player game, but you
        should probably include some of the Lone Impostor settings to keep the balance right.\n\n
        Lone Impostor: With just one Impostor, the crew has a significant advantage. The best way
        to balance this is to have quick kill cooldowns of 15 seconds or less, long kill distance,
        only 1 emergency meeting, and Impostor vision should be at least 0.5 higher than crewmate
        vision, arguably even more.\n\n
        Three Impostors: Here, the Impostors have the advantage. For that reason, you want long
        kill cooldowns, probably of over 40 seconds, and only a short kill distance. It might be
        best to stick with just the 1 emergency meeting, as frequent meetings being called can
        abuse the long kill cooldown and make it too difficult for the Impostors to work. Impostor
        vision can still be higher, though only by around 0.2. When playing with two Impostors, a
        balance between these two approaches is advisable.\n\n
        General Advice\n\n
        You want to try and keep a balance between whether your game favors the Impostors or the
        crewmates. Long meeting cooldowns, short kill cooldowns, no visual tasks, don\'t confirm
        ejects, long kill distance, and lots of long tasks will favor the Impostor.\n
        The opposite of each of those settings favors the crewmates. If you\'re playing a few games
        together, tweak the settings each time to figure out what balance works for you.
    </string>
    <!-- CREWMATE TIPS -->
    <string name="crewmate_how_to_play_text">
        To join a game, select either online or local. From here, you can choose whether to create
        or join a game, and whether you’re searching for a game with 1, 2, or 3 Impostors.\n\n 1.
        You will not know if you are a crewmate or Impostor until the game starts.\n2. To control
        your character, it’s either keyboard and mouse or just mouse, while everyone’s speed can
        be.\n3. On phones, there is an analogue stick touch pad for moving.\n4. To do tasks, you
        need to walk to the correct room and either click the object directly or click the ‘Use’
        button in the bottom right corner. From there, each task is fairly self explanatory.\n5.
        If you find a dead body, you can click ‘Report’ in the bottom right corner. This will call
        a team meeting, where you can discuss where you found the body, discover if anyone else was
        killed, and share your suspicions. You do not have to report a body if you see one, though.
        \n6. You can also call an emergency meeting from a button in the middle of the map.\n7.
        After the discussions, you vote. You can elect to skip a vote. If skipping has the most
        votes or there is a tie, nobody will be ejected.\n8. To win the game, you must complete all
        tasks before the Impostor kills the crew.\n9. Once you are killed, you can continue to
        complete tasks as a ghost to help your team, but you cannot communicate.
    </string>

    <string name="crewmate_tips_and_tricks_text">
        1. Complete Tasks\nSounds basic, but this is how you win. Try completing a group of tasks in
        one area at a time. Not only will this allow you to monitor an area better, but also get a
        lot done efficiently.\n\nTasks are crucial to victory as a crewmate. The whole crew needs
        to either complete all of the tasks before the Impostor kills everyone off, or to vote
        all of the Impostors out.\n\n
        2. Take Breaks Between Tasks\nYeah, this contradicts the tip above, but make sure you don\’t
        have a laser focus on the tasks, otherwise you\’ll never figure out the Impostor.\n\n
        3. Be Aware of Your Sight Lines\nMost tasks take up the whole screen, leaving you blind,
        and some take a long time to complete. Be aware not to do these if someone suspicious is
        around.\n\nConsider doing the tasks you know will take more time first when you\'ve got the
        best chance to be around a lot of people.\n\n
        4. Safety in Numbers\nTraveling with a person you trust means its much harder for an
        Impostor to kill you, but you may well be pairing up with an Impostor yourself. Tread
        carefully. If you can be with more than one other person you\'ll probably be better off.\n\n
        5. Let Someone See You do a Visual Task\nMost tasks aren\’t visual - as in others can\’t tell
        if you\’re doing them - but a few are. Scanning in the MedBay, for example. If someone sees
        you, they know for sure you\’re not an Impostor.\n\nKeep an eye on people who complete
        critical tasks too. For instance, if you\'re on your way to fix the lights or power,
        remember who was there before you and take note of whether or not they completed the task
        before you had a chance to. Did anyone show up after you had completed the task? Almost
        more important, who didn\'t show up?\n\n
        6. Ask Questions\nLots of accusations fly in the chat, but watch out that Impostors will
        often accuse someone innocent. Don\’t just follow the first accusation, it could be
        Impostors trying to thin the herd.\n\n
        7. Keep a lookout\nStrange behavior doesn\’t necessarily an Impostor, but it is definitely
        worth making a mental note of.\n\nOdd behavior:\n\n- Standing near vents for no reason
        \n- Standing in corners of a room away from tasks\n- Not being able to clearly articulate
        what tasks they were working on during a round\n- Making excuses for not finishing things
        because of reasons outside the game\n- Staying in only one or two rooms where there aren\'t
        many tasks\n- Standing near doors but not entering rooms frequently\n\nSome of these actions
        could be done just because a player is inexperienced. Still, be cautious!\n\n
        8. Skip\nDon\’t be afraid to skip a vote if no one has convinced you, the road to winning
        comes through completing tasks.\n\n
        9. Know the map\nThis is needed to get the fastest route to complete tasks and also to react
        to sabotage.
    </string>

    <string name="the_skeld_tasks_guide_title">The Skeld tasks guide</string>
    <string name="the_skeld_tasks_guide_text">
        The Skeld is one of three maps in Among Us, but as the default map is probably the best
        known. Here, we\’ll explore every room on the ship, detailing the tasks in each room,
        methods of sabotage, and any tips each room can offer. We\’ll list them alphabetically
        here, and for tasks which happen in multiple rooms, they\’re listed in the room they start
        in. Once you do one half of a multi room task, you\’ll get a yellow arrow on screen leading
        you to the other one.\n\nAdmin\n\nSwipe Card - This occurs on the right hand side of the
        table in the admin room, and is relatively simple. It won\’t count if you go too fast or
        too slow, but other than that, it\’s a straightforward swipe.\nFix Wires - There are three
        different wires tasks which involve matching up colored wires. One of them is in the
        corridor into the Admin room.\nUpload Data From - There are several Upload Data tasks,
        which each start in different rooms. However, they all finish at the WiFi symbol in the
        corridor of the Admin room, right next to the wire box.\nAdmin Room Tip: In the admin room
        you can also keep track of who\’s in what room with the device on the left hand side of the
        table, which is very useful for checking who might be lying during Impostor discussions.\n\n
        Cafeteria\n\nUpload Data From The Cafeteria - One of those data tasks that finishes in the
        Admin room begins in the Cafeteria. Select the WiFi board in the top right corner, click
        upload, and wait a few seconds for the transfer. Afterwards, head to the Admin room to
        upload it.\nFix Wires - Another wire task is on the left hand wall of the cafeteria.\n
        Empty Garbage - This is a two part task, with the first switch right next to the Upload
        Data task. Click the switch, then hold down the lever to empty the chute. After this, head
        down to the Storage room to repeat the task.\n\nCommunications\n\nUpload Data From
        Communications - Just like the Cafeteria one, you have to take it to the Admin room
        afterwards. Let\’s not get ahead of ourselves though, first you have to grab the data from
        the left wall as soon as you enter the room.\n\nElectrical\n\nUpload Data From Electrical
        - Same as the other data tasks, you need to grab data from the WiFi panel then head back
        to admin\nCalibrate Distributor - Select the box with the high voltage sign on the right
        hand side of the room and line up the three rectangles spinning around the circle. They
        all have to stop on the right, connected to the distributor plugs.\nDivert Power To -
        There are several Divert Power To.. tasks, and they all start on the back wall of
        Electrical. Select the control panel, and then flip the switch to divert power to
        whichever room you need. From there, you just need to find the panel (the yellow arrow
        will guide you) and flip the connector in the center.\nUpper Engine - In the middle of the
        back wall\nLower Engine - On the left as soon as you enter\nWeapons - At the near side of
        the right wall\nShields - On the right as soon as you enter\nNavigation - In the left
        corner\nCommunication - On the right as soon as you enter\nO2 - On the left as soon as
        you enter\nSecurity - On the angled right wall.\nElectrical Tip: This is a small room
        with potentially a lot of tasks, which makes it prime Impostor real estate. Get out as
        fast as you can as a crewmate, or use this as a hunting spot as an Impostor.\n\nEngines\n\n
        Align Engine Output - This involves hitting both Upper and Lower Engines and selecting the
        box on the nearside of the engines, and lining up the computer mouse shaped object so it
        fits between the parallel lines.\n\nMedbay\n\nSubmit Scan - This involves standing on the
        circular podium and is one of the game\’s most straightforward tasks. It also doesn\’t block
        your vision like some others, so means there’s less chance of an Impostor getting the drop
        on you.\nInspect Sample - Select the device on the back wall then follow the button
        prompts. There is a real-world 60 second wait here while the machine processes the sample,
        so you can use this time to be on the look out for any suspicious behavior. Just make sure
        to head back and select the odd sample out.\n\nNavigation\n\nFix Wires - The third wires
        box is on the left as soon as you enter.\nUpload Data From Navigation - The data point is
        just to the right of the wires box, and again needs to be taken to Admin.\nChart Course -
        There are two control panels at the back of Navigation. The left hand one lets you chart a
        course, and you need to zig zag the ship along the lines provided.\nStabilize Steering -
        This is the second - and larger - of the two control panels in Navigation, and involves
        you selecting the crosshair target in the middle of the screen.\n\nO2\n\nEmpty Chute -
        Pull the lever on the back wall to empty the chute. The second part of the task takes
        place in Storage.\nClean O2 Filter - This is the vent like object near the back of the
        room. Click it and drag the leaves out of the grate.\n\nReactor\n\nUnlock Manifolds - This
        task is the little bar at the back of the room. Select it and then click the numbers 1-10
        in order.\nStart Reactor - This is the control panel next to the glowing tubes (ie the
        reactor). There is a sequence, first with one flashing light adding one each time until
        five flashing lights, that needs to be repeated in order to complete the task.\n\nSecurity\n
        \nNo tasks besides the diverting power task which begins in Electrical.\nSecurity Tip:
        There are cameras in this room; use them to try and spot an Imposter behaving strangely.\n\n
        Shields\n\nPrime Shields - This is the little speaker box in the bottom corner of the
        room. Select it and click each of the red hexagons.\n\nStorage\n\nFuel Engines - This is
        a bit of a long task, but the upside is you get to see a bit more of the ship and might
        spot the Impostor… or you could be killed. Anyway. Grab the gas can from Storage and use
        the button in the bottom right to fill it up. Head to either Upper or Lower Engines to
        fill the engines up with the nozzle on the nearside, then head back to Storage to repeat
        the process, this time heading to the other engine.\n\nWeapons\n\nClear Asteroids -
        Another task which can take a bit longer, this one is at least more fun. Several asteroids
        will come flying past the screen once you click the seat and joy sticks in the middle;
        hit 20 of them to complete this task.
    </string>

    <string name="mirahq_tasks_guide_title">Mira HQ tasks guide</string>
    <string name="mirahq_tasks_guide_text">
        Mira HQ is one of three maps in Among Us, and is probably the second most popular after
        The Skeld, though it has more unique areas to it. Here, we\’ll explore every room on the
        ship, detailing the tasks in each room, methods of sabotage, and any tips each room can
        offer. We\’ll list them alphabetically here, and for tasks which happen in multiple rooms,
        they\’re listed in the room they start in. Once you do one half of a multi room task,
        you\’ll get a yellow arrow on screen leading you to the other one.\n\nAdmin\n\n
        The Admin room in Mira HQ has three tasks:\nPrime Shields - From the console at the bottom
        of the room, click and choose all of the red shapes.\nChart Course - Go to the controls
        at the right corner of the room, and drag the ship along the dotted course.\n
        ID Code - Select the table as soon as you enter to bring up the code entry. Select the
        card from your wallet and enter the code printed on it into the key pad.\n
        Admin room tip: You can use the central table here to view how many people are in each
        room, which can help in Impostor discussions, or in finding folks to hunt if you are
        the Impostor.\n\nBalcony\n\nClear Asteroids - At the console to the left of the balcony,
        click to activate the asteroids then keep shooting until you\’ve cleared 20\n
        Measure Weather - This time, go the right of the balcony. Click the switch, then
        activate the terminal and wait for it to finish measuring.\n\nCafeteria\n\nEmpty Garbage -
        Head to the lever on the wall and hold it down until the screen is empty.\nBuy Beverage -
        Click the vending machine at the back of the room. There will be a scribbled drawing of
        the beverage to buy; find it and input the right code.\n\nCommunications\n\n
        There are no tasks here aside from Divert Power, which begins in the Reactor\n
        Communications Tip: Use the door log to track crew movements around the ship.\n\n
        Greenhouse\n\nClean O2 Filter - Click the glass chamber at the back of the room and
        drag all of the leaves out of the vent.\n\nLocker Room\n\nFix Wiring - This is a three
        part task which starts outside the Locker Room. Click the panel then line up the wires
        across either side by matching the colors. After this, you\’ll need to head to the
        Greenhouse and to the Reactor to finish the task.\nLocker Room Tip: This room contains
        the entrance to the airlock.\n\nLaboratory\n\nAssemble Artefact - This happens on the
        table at the top of the room. You\’ll need to arrange the pieces of crystal into a jigsaw
        to finish the tasks.\nSort Samples - At the bottom table, there are three boxes. You\’ll
        need to put shiny geodes in the gem box, animal fossils in the paw print box, and plant
        fossils in the leaf box. There\’s usually two of each.\n\nLaunch Pad\n\n
        Fuel Engines - Click the terminal on the left until the gas canister comes up.
        Hold down the bottom button until the engine is full.\nRun Diagnostics - Use the console
        on the left and begin the task. It will take a long time, almost a minute, for this to go
        through. You can leave the terminal and come back, but the task will not register as
        complete until you select it one final time to choose the anomaly.\n\nMedBay\n\n
        Submit Scan - Stand on the central platform and begin the task. You must remain still
        during the scan for it to work.\n\nOffice\n\nProcess Data - Select the computer at the
        back of the room, then wait while the data uploads itself.\n\nReactor\n\n
        Start Reactor - Go up to the actual reactor in the middle of the room. Once clicked, it\’s
        a simple case of following the sequence of flashes until you\’ve done this five times.\n
        Unlock Manifold - Click the keypad on the left of the room, then tap the numbers 1-10
        in sequence.\nDivert Power To - There are a lot of tasks like this which begin in the
        Reactor. You\’ll need to click the control panel at the bottom of the room, then choose
        which room to divert the power to. Afterwards, head to that room to finish the task.\n
        1.Admin - On the back wall\n2.Cafeteria - In the top left corner\n3.Communications -
        On the wall as you enter\n4.Greenhouse - At the mini console to the far left of the room\n
        5.Laboratory - On the left as soon as you enter\n6.Launch Pad - The mini console on the
        left of the doorway\n7.MedBay - In the middle of the back wall\n8.Office - At the mini
        console in front of the computer\n\nStorage\n\nWater Plants - First, you need to select
        the watering can at the back of the room. This will bring up a new screen, where you\’ll
        need to, um, click the watering can again. After this, head to the Greenhouse and click
        the plants on the right to finish the task.
    </string>

    <!-- IMPOSTOR TIPS -->
    <string name="impostor_how_to_play_text">
        To join a game, select either online or local. From here, you can choose whether to create
        or join a game, and whether you’re searching for a game with 1, 2, or 3 Impostors.\n\n
        Select which of the three maps you want to play on.\n1. You will not know if you are a
        crewmate or Impostor until the game starts.\n 2. To control your character, it’s either
        keyboard and mouse or just mouse, while everyone’s speed can be adjusted by the host.
        What you choose is just personal preference.\n3. On phones, there is a analogue stick touch
        pad for moving.\n 4. You will be given fake tasks by the game; pretend to do them to blend
        in.\n 5. To kill someone, get close enough to them for the ‘Kill’ button in the bottom right
        hand corner to light up.\n 6. There is a cooldown timer between kills, which can be
        customized by the host.\n 7. You can either report the body yourself, or run away to take
        the suspicion off you.\n 8. You can still participate in discussions and should try to throw
        suspicion off you.\n9. You can sabotage the ship, either by locking down certain rooms or by
        setting off faults.\n10. Some faults - such as turning off the lights - make it harder for
        crewmates to complete tasks, while others - such as turning off the oxygen - will kill them
        if they do not fix it in time.\n 11. You can use the vents to get around the ship faster,
        but if anyone spots you, they will know you are an Impostor.\n 12. To win the game, you need
        to kill off the crew.
    </string>

    <string name="impostor_tips_and_tricks_text">
        1. Try to Blend In\nKnow where tasks take place. This is the most important part of being a
        believable "crewmate" as the Imposter! Pretend to do tasks (and let people see you) by
        standing by and waiting. The game even gives you fake ones, so you don\’t duplicate anyone
        else\’s tasks.\n\nWhen you give your alibi, be sure to mention the \"tasks\" you completed
        and where. Just giving the locations you were at during the round isn\'t convincing. If you
        can back them up with specific tasks you\'ll be far more convincing.\n\nYou can learn tasks
        for each map by playing in the practice mode. Definitely take the time to do this if you\'re
        trying to best experienced friends.\n\n
        2. J\’accuse!\nThere is often limited time to discuss the Impostor after a body is discovered
        , so try and throw the suspicion elsewhere. Don\’t be too obvious (like don\’t say you saw
        them kill when they obviously didn\’t), but do try and upset the balance.\n\n
        3. Follow An Accusation\nOccasionally, a crewmate will accuse the wrong person. When this
        happens, you want to double down on this and get them out. With multi Impostors, you can
        even team up and accuse.\n\n
        4. Watch the Kill Counter\nYou can\’t just kill whenever you want, as there\’s a kill cooldown
        timer. Don\’t go in for the kill if it means trailing someone for 15 seconds.\n\nBe strategic
        about who you kill too. If someone was accusing you of being an Imposter, it could be more
        fishy if they suddenly turn up dead the next round.\n\n
        5. Sabotage\nLock players in, set off faults… anything to delay them completing their tasks.
        Locking players in together can cause suspicion too. Do this strategically. Maybe even
        lock yourself in with someone you don\'t plan to kill so that you\'re safe.\n\n
        6. Set Traps\nIf you sabotage the O2 in The Skeld, for example, you know crewmates are going
        to rush there. But some will ignore the alarm and work on their tasks on the other side,
        aware that other crew mates will handle it. You can linger away from the sabotage in the
        hopes that someone unguarded will walk by.\n\n
        7. Vent with Caution\nVents are a great way to get around, especially if you\’ve trapped
        someone in a room, but if anyone sees you, they know you\’re the Impostor. The animation for
        an Imposter popping out of a vent is very obvious if someone sees it.\n\n
        8. Don\’t be afraid to act odd\nEveryone is trying to figure the Impostor out, so everyone is
        going to wander around a little bit. Don\’t be afraid to be a little odd, especially if
        you\’re playing with IRL friends and are having a few games.
    </string>

    <string name="the_skeld_sabotages_vents_title">The Skeld - Sabotages/Vents</string>
    <string name="the_skeld_sabotages_vents_text">
        Vents\n\nOnly the impostor has access to the vents, so be careful not to be spotted going
        into them. They do help you get around quicker though, and escape any areas you might
        have locked down. The various tunnel links can be found below.\n- Admin-Cafeteria-Corridor
        (between Weapons and Shields)\n- Weapons-Navigation\n- Shields-Navigation\n- Electrical-
        Security-MedBay\n- Lower Engine-Reactor\n- Upper Engine-Reactor\n\nSabotages\n\n
        The most common way to sabotage is to lockdown a room, but that is an inconvenience more
        than anything else, and will only delay the crew’s progress. Upper Engine, Lower Engine,
        Security, MedBay, Electrical, Cafeteria, and Storage can all be locked down.\n\n
        You can also set off the Reactor, which will kill the crew if not disabled in time, turn
        off the O2 which will suffocate them if not fixed, turn off the lights to impair vision,
        or take out the communications to disable the security cameras.
    </string>

    <string name="mirahq_sabotages_vents_title">Mira HQ Sabotages/Vents</string>
    <string name="mirahq_sabotages_vents_text">
        Vents\n\nThe vents are especially interesting in Mira HQ, as they all link together as
        one labyrinth. Below is a list of all the rooms with vents in them.\n
        - Balcony\n- MedBay\n- Reactor\n- Launch Pad\n- Locker Room\n- Decontamination Corridor\n
        - Cafeteria\n- Admin\n- Greenhouse\n- Office\n- Laboratory\n\nSabotage\n\n
        When playing as the Impostor, you have more tools at your disposal than just killing your
        foes or using vents. You can also sabotage various rooms to help earn yourself that victory.
        You can\’t seal doors, but you can turn off the O2 or sabotage the Reactor, both of which
        will kill the crew if they\’re not fixed in time. You can also use the Office to turn off
        the lights, decreasing visibility, and sabotage Communications to scramble to Admin room
        locator and the door log.
    </string>
</resources>